Guide to the New York Wine & Grape Foundation records, 1968-2004.
New York Wine & Grape Foundation records}
- Series IV. Wineries
  - North Salem Vineyard, Inc, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Pallante and Son Wine Cellars, Inc, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Peconic Bay Vineyards, Inc., 1985 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Pindat Vineyards Winery, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Plane's Cayuga Vineyard, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Poplar Ridge Vineyards, Inc, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Rolling Vineyards, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Royal Kedem Winery, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Schloss Doepken Winery (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Seagram Wine Company, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Seagram Campaign, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Vinifera Wine Cellars, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Wagner Vineyards, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Taylor Wine Company Inc, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Walker Valley Vineyards, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Wickham Vineyards Ltd., 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Widmer's Wine Cellars, Inc, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Hermann J Wiemer Vineyard, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Windsor Vineyards, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Woodbury Vineyards, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Woodstock Winery, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Styrofoam wine caddy, MU-2074 (Box 13)
  - Vinifera Wine Cellars Ltd, 1986-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Canadaiga Wine Company (Widmer's/Batavia/Manischewitz), 1985-1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Adair Vineyards, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Amberleaf Vineyards, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ambrosia Farms Corporation, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Arbor Hill Grapery, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Baldwin Vineyards, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Banfi Vintners, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Barrington Champagne Company, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bedell Cellars, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Benmarl Wine Company, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bidwell Vineyards, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Brimstone Hill Vineyards, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - The Bridgehampton Winery, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Brotherhood Winery, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Bully Hill Vineyard, Inc, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Cana Creation, Inc, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Canadaigua Wine Company, Inc., 1982-1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Casa Larga Vineyards, 1987-1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Cascade Mountain Vineyards, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Castel Grisch, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Chadwick Bay Wine Company, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Chateau de Rheims, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Chateau Frank, Inc, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Chateau Lafayette Remeau, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Clinton Vineyards Inc, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Cottage Vineyards, Inc, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Eaton Vineyards, Inc, 1987-1992 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Finger Lakes Wineries, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Glenora Wine Cellars, 1986-1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Gold Seal, 1974-1981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Gristina Vineyards, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Hargrave Vineyards, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Hazlitt 1852 Vineyards, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Hermann J Wiemer Vineyard, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Hunt Country Vineyards, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Joseph Victori Wines, Inc, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Joseph Zakon Winery - Crown Regal Wine Cellars, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Kedem Royal Wine Company, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Knapp Vineyards, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Lakewood Vineyards, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Lenz Winery, December 14 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - La Reve, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - McGregor Vineyard and Winery, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Merritt Estate Winery Inc, 1987-1991 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Millbrook Vineyards, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - North Fork Winery, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - North Salem Vineyard, Inc, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Palmer Vineyards, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Paumanoak Vineyards, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Pindar Vineyards, 1986-1992 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Plane's Cayuga Vineyard, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Poplar Ridge Vineyards, Inc, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Prejean Winery, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Rivendell Winery, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Six Mile Creek Vineyard, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Soundview Vineyards, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Swedish Hill Vineyard and Winery, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Taylor - Great Western Gold Seal Winery Visitor Center, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Winery Guide, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Thorpe Vineyard, Inc (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Treleaven Winery, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Wagner Vineyards, 1986-1992 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Walker Valley Vineyards, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Widmer's Wine Cellars, Inc, 1988-1992 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Woodbury Vineyards, 1982-1990 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Benmarl Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Brimstone Hill Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Black Bear Farm Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Blueberry Sky Farm Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bully Hill Vineyard, Inc, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Casa Larga Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cascade Mountain Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Castello Di Borghese, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Cayuga Ridge Estate, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Chateau Frank, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Chateau Lafayette Remeau, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Chateau Renaissance, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Channing Daughters, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Clinton Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Corey Creek, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Demarest Hill Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Duck Walk Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Chateau Frank Champagne, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Earle Estates, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - El Paso Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Finger Lakes Champagne House, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Fox Run Vineyards, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Fulkerson Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Giancarelli Bros Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Glenora Wine Cellars, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Goosewatch Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Hazlitt Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Hermann J Wiemer Vineyard, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Heron Hill Vineyard, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Hosmer Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Hunt Country Vineyards, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Jamesport Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Joseph Zakon Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Keuka Overlook Wine Cellars, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Johnson Estate Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Keuka Spring Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - King Ferry Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Knapp Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Lakeshore Winery, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Lakewood Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - La Moreaux Landing, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Larry's Vineyard and Farm Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Laurel Lake Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - The Lenz Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Long Point Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Lucas Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - North Salem Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Macari Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Martha Clara Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Martin's Honey Farm, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - McGregor Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Merritt Estate Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Millbrook Vineyards and Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Old Brookville Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Osprey's Dominion Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Palmer Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Paumanoak Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Pazdar Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Pellegrini Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Peconic Bay Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Pindar Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Pleasant Valley Wine Company, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Prejean Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Pugliese Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Raphael Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Red Newt Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Rivendell Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Royal Wine Co., 2001 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Schneider Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Shalestone Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Sheldrake Point Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Silver Thread Vineyard, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Six Mile Creek Vineyard, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Standing Stone Vineyard, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Stone Age Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Swedish Hill Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Ternhaven Cellars, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Thorpe Vineyard, Inc, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Torrey Ridge Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Warwick Valley Winery, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Wagner Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Wolffer Estate, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Woodbury Vineyards, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Willow Creek Winery, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Windsor Vineyards, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Wine Magazines, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 87)
- Series V. Trade Shows
  - Winery Update Pt 1, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Winery Update Pt 2, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Calendar Updates and Press Releases, 2001-2003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Calendar Events, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Wine Competitions, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Wine Competition, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Wines of the Americas, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Business Cards From Trade Shows (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Wineries Unlimited Seminar and Tradeshow, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Trade Shows, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New York State Restaurant Association, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - New York State Restaurant Association, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New York State Restaurant Association, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NYSRA Buffalo, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - New York State Restaurant Association, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - New York State Restaurant Association, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - NYSRA Meetings and Wineries, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - NYSRA Trade Show, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - National Restaurant Association Restaurant Hotel/Motel Show, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - New York State Restaurant Association, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - National Restaurant Association Restaurant Hotel/Motel Show, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Trade Shows, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Trade Show Questionnaires, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Restaurant and Hospitality Expo, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Trade Shows Long Island, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Trade Shows, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Viticulture Trade Show, 2000-2003 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - New York Restaurant Association, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Series VI. Legislation
  - Legislation, Miscellaneous, 1975-1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - California Reciprocal Tax, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Farm Winery Tax, 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Legislation, Sale of Wines in Grocery Stores, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The Model Alcoholic Beverage Control Act, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Legislation, Sale of Wines, NY Wine Council Letter Campaign, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Legislation, Sale of NY State Wines in Grocery Stores, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Legislation, Sale of NY State Wines in Grocery Stores, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Legislation, Sale of Wine in Grocery Stores, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Winery Deregulation, 1976-1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Legislation, Wine Equity Act, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Wine Tastings Bill, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Law, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - New York State Agriculture Committees, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - New York State, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural Assessment in New York State, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, Finance, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - NYS Assembly Speaker Mel Miller, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, Commissioner, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - The Journal, New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1987, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - New York State of Equalization and Assessment, Agricultural Use Values, 1972-1983 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - New York State of Equalization and Assessment, Agricultural Use Values, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - New York State of Equalization and Assessment, Agricultural Use Values, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - New York State of Equalization and Assessment, Agricultural Use Values, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - New York State Board of Equalization and Assessment, 1984-1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Associated New York State Food Processors, Inc, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo, Correspondence and Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo, Correspondence and Clippings, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo, Correspondence and Clippings, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo, Correspondence and Clippings, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo, Correspondence and Clippings, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Key Legislative Contacts, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Agenda, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - New York State Legislators, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - New York State Assembly, Correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - New York State Assembly, Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lobbying, 1980-1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lobbying, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Albany Trips, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Political Contributions, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - New York State Legislation, 1987-1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - New York State Legislation, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Political Donation Requests, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - New York State Representatives, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - United States Congressmen, Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - US Senator Alfonse D'Amato, New York State Farm Harvest Day Correspondence, 1982-1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - US Senator Daniel Moynihan Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - US Congressman Stan Lundine, 1982-1986 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Winegrape Growers of America - Schramm, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Status of National Agricultural Marketing and Bargaining Legislation, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - USDA Reports, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - American Grape Growers Alliance, Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - American Grape Growers Alliance, Newspaper Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Committee Activities and Records, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Tax Credit Bill, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - State Regulations (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to NYS Legislature, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Bottle Law, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Legislation, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Agenda, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bills, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Bargaining Bill, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Drinking Age Change to 21, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - NYSWGG Tim Trezise, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Department of Labor, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Competitions, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - NYS Liquor Regulations, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Legislation, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Legislation, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Legislation and Lobbying, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Assembly Bills, 1979-1985 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Senate Bills, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Legislation, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - New York Legislature, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Assembly, 1984-1990 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Michael Braggman, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Assemblyman Combe (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Dan Davidsen Assemblyman, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Assemblyman Feldman, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Assemblyman Fink, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Richard J Keane, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Assemblyman Nozzolio, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - NYS Assemblyman McCann (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Mel Miller NYS Assembly Speaker, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - NYS Assembly Pillittere, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - NYS Assembly Rappleyea, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - NYS Assembly Robach, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - NYS Assembly Rob Smith, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - NYS Assembly Talomie, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Walsh, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - NYS Assembly Winner, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Senate Tasting, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Special Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Senator Anderson, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Senators Johnson and Houghton (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Senator Kehoe, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Senator Kidder, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Senator Kuhe, 1985-1991 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Senator Ohrenstein, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Senator Parment, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Senator J Present, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Senator Riford, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Louise Slaughter, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Assemblyman Tonko, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - NYS Senate, 1981-1985 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Bill Smith, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Mary Wilber, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Wine Industry, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Exports, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Imports, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Imports, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Imports, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Commerce Dept, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Wine Grape Marketing Order Background, 1968-1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Wine Grape Marketing Order, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Marketing Order Contract and Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Wine Grape Marketing Order, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    State of New York Department of Agriculture and Markets File.
  - Implementation Marketing Order, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Board, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Opposition, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Wine Grape Marketing Order Budget and Expenses, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Wine Coolers, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Wine Coolers, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Wine Coolers, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Wine Coolers, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Wine Cooler Lawsuit, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Wine Cooler Lawsuit, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Legislation, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Legislation, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - House Agriculture Committee, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Lead, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Series VII. Public Relations
  - Rand Public Relations Proposal, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rand Public Relations, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Rand Public Relations, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Rand Public Relations Press Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Rand Public Relations Editorial Leads, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Rand Public Relations Photographs and Slides, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, Uncork New York!, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, Finance, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Ketchum Reports, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    New York Wine and Grape Foundation Report/Program Recommendations and Interfiles Materials
  - Ketchum Public Relations, Grape Juice, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Ketchum Public Relations Radio Promotion, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Ketchum Public Relations Restaurant Promotion, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Ketchum Advertising, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, Table Grape Questionnaires, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, Table Grapes, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Ketchum Public Relations, Table Grapes, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - NYS Wine and Grape Market Research, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Wine Handbook, Sonoma County Promotional Material, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Wine Marketing, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Marketing, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Market Research Firms, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Marketing Proposals, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Series VIII. Marketing Research
  - COMTEC, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Diamandis Communications, Inc. Lead Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - New York State Wine and Grape Market Research V1, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - New York State Wine and Grape Market Research V2, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - New York State Wine and Grape Market Tabulations, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - New York State Wine and Grape Foundation Briefing Packet, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Press Releases, 1982-1988 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - I Love NY Spring Festival, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Press Releases, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Uncork New York, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Press Releases, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Uncork New York, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Farm Bureau Perspective Radio Show, cassette tape plus letter, September 15, 1986; tr-10108 (Box 23)
  - The Grapevine Fine Wine Show, cassette tape, September 3, 2000; tr-10109 (Box 23)
  - New York Wine and Grape Foundation 10 @:60, cassette tape, tr-10110 (Box 23)
  - New York Wine and Grape Foundation 10 @:60, cassette tape, tr-10111 (Box 23)
  - New York Wine and Grape Foundation 10 @:60, cassette tape, tr-10112 (Box 23)
  - Allstar Wine and Liqour, Uncork New York 60, cassette tape, November 1999; tr-10113 (Box 23)
  - Seneca Lake Wine Trail, VHS tape, V-7041 (Box 23)